Fine.
You hit me for some rich old man.
Zhao Wenjuan,
you're really something.
I don't want your filthy money.
Just you wait.
Who are you?
Do we know each other?
No.
Then we can get to know each other.
A gentleman doesn't accept handouts.
It's not a handout.
I'm offering it.
You've been yelling for a while.
You must be thirsty.
Thanks.
But there's no need
to get to know each other.
Let's just exchange names, okay?
I'm Gao Yayan.
What's your name?
Bai Xiaosi.
Is that okay?
Thanks for the treat.
Help me look someone up.
A kid,
about 16 or 17,
named Bai Xiaosi.
Shen Xi,
open the door.
I have something to tell you, Shen Xi.
Shen Xi,
are you home?
Group 2, any findings at the stairs?
Captain Weng,
nothing found.
Group 3, what's the situation
on the surveillance?
Captain Weng,
the surveillance shows
Shen Xi returned to the neighborhood
nine minutes ago,
entered the building,
and hasn't come out since.
Group 3, keep an eye on the surveillance,
especially the building entrance
and her car.
Shen Xi is very likely
to escape in the chaos.
Copy that, Captain Weng.
Someone come up and get the door unlocked.
Copy that.
Jiang,
the bedroom.
Captain Weng,
Shen Xi's car is at the main gate.
Team 4, intercept and make the arrest.
Copy that.
This is the place.
She came up from that building,
crossed this platform,
and went down the other one,
dodging our blockade.
Jiang!
Where's Jiang Dahai?
He dropped the ball at the worst time.
It's fine. Our guys are on her tail.
She won't get away.
Yanhu Checkpoint is in position.
Target vehicle spotted.
Get out of the car!
Get out now!
Hands off the steering wheel.
Take off your mask.
Captain Weng,
we intercepted the car.
But it's the wrong person.
It's a guy.
It's that fake cop from before,
Bai Xiaosi.
Him again. Bai Xiaosi.
Bring him back for interrogation.
Copy that.
Jiang Dahai,
where did you go?
Get back here.
Shen Xi,
where are you going?
Decoys,
diversions,
and misdirection.
You played your tricks well, Ms. Shen.
Tell me,
where are you planning to go?
You flatter me, Officer Li.
I just wanted to take a trip
and clear my head.
You guys keep tracking me down
and questioning me.
Between the car accident and the suicide,
it's just too much.
I just want to get some fresh air.
Why hide from us, then?
I know
cooperating with your investigation
is every citizen's duty.
But to be honest,
I really don't want
to deal with you anymore.
You went to all this trouble
just because you didn't want
to deal with us?
You even dragged Bai Xiaosi into this
to act as your decoy.
Do you have any idea how old he is?
He's a minor
without a driver's license.
This kid
tricked me with a fake driver's license.
You mean
you didn't know he was underage
and couldn't get a license?
Of course.
I wouldn't
risk my own life
when hiring a driver.
He did show me his license.
How was I supposed to know it was fake?
I'm not a traffic cop like you guys.
I don't have a pair of sharp eyes.
0451, You Xiaosi.
Remember me?
Of course,
Officer Weng.
Last time I went to the detention center,
you escorted me there yourself.
Good that you remember.
What happened this time?
How did you get mixed up with Shen Xi?
When you're out of luck,
everything goes wrong.
So you're saying
it's just bad luck that you got caught
doing something illegal?
That's not what I meant.
After I got out last time,
I wanted to find a way to make a living.
I couldn't shoot videos pretending
to be a traffic cop anymore.
That's illegal.
So I thought about
working part-time as a driver.
A driver? What kind of driver?
Are you even 18?
I get it.
You stopped pretending to be a traffic cop
and started dealing fake IDs, right?
Let me tell you, that's just as illegal.
No, no, no.
I just bought a cover.
When the employer wanted to see it,
I'd show it.
If I could fool them, great.
If not, oh well.
Tell me,
what's your relationship
with the car owner, Shen Xi?
Why did you pretend to be her
and drive away?
I told you,
she's my employer.
I wanted to find a driver to accompany me
on a trip out of town for a few days.
I saw his message online
and arranged to meet at a cafe.
You're Babbling Brook, right?
I'm Xiaosi Bubai.
Kid,
I'm looking for a girl,
not someone pretending to be one, okay?
Don't worry.
With a little dressing up
today,
I'll look more real than a real girl.
How old are you, kid?
Are you of age?
Nineteen.
Being young is great.
Young guys are considerate,
sweet, and obedient.
Do you have a driver's license?
Can you drive?
Of course.
I wouldn't take the job
if I didn't have the skills.
Let me see it.
Let's agree on the price first.
The price is negotiable.
He interrupted me at the time,
and I got distracted.
I figured
he was just an innocent kid
who wouldn't lie to me.
So I didn't ask about it again.
It's that simple.
Any problem,
officer?
Yes, there is.
Since you hired him,
why did he drive away
instead of waiting for you
when you went upstairs
to get your luggage?
That's because I suddenly
got a call from her.
The boss said to pick someone up
at the Chuanyun Road intersection
in five minutes,
and she'd pay me extra.
Didn't you see the police
chasing and blocking you
when you were driving?
You were moving forward, backward,
and even trying to turn left
at that intersection.
Why didn't you stop
when you saw the police?
I was scared.
I didn't know what it was about this time.
I don't have a driver's license,
so I could only try to run away.
I asked him to fetch something
at the intersection.
It was indeed to distract you.
Because I didn't want to deal
with you guys anymore.
I'm even sick of it.
Is that okay?
Yes.
Did you get all that down? Got it.
I hope you can give me
a reasonable explanation
for the next question too.
Go ahead.
Xiao Ze
invited you to a dance drama.
You didn't show up.
Where did you go?
I was performing.
Weren't you there that day?
I was one of the masked actors
on stage.
Then why didn't you say so
when I asked you that day?
I'm sorry, Officer Li.
I don't know
whose memory is failing here.
As I recall,
you never asked me that question.
You just asked me
if I went to the show
with Xiao Ze that day,
and then
asked me
about going to the woods the next day.
So you know the dance drama director,
Song Yanfei,
right?
He is the person
I hate the most.
The year I graduated from college,
I was drifting in Beijing,
hoping to find a job in a film crew.
Okay,
I'll wait to hear from you.
Looking forward to working with you.
Next.
Come in.
Hello.
You must be the director.
How should I address you?
Yes, I am.
Just call me Song Yanfei,
or Director Song.
Got it. Hello, Director Song.
Here is my resume.
My name is Shen Xi.
Shen Xi.
Please, take a seat.
I graduated from the acting department
of the Dance Academy.
I can dance and act,
and I really look forward
to working with you.
Well,
through our conversation,
we found out
we were from the same hometown.
That instantly brought us closer.
At that time,
he was preparing
for the dance drama,
"Circle".
He explained the play to me,
and I was completely captivated.
I loved this play so much.
I told him
I'd dance in it
even for free,
as long as I had food to eat.
From that day on,
we worked hard together
to revise the script,
meet actors, and seek investment.
During this process,
we grew closer and closer.
Until that day,
he confessed his feelings to me.
I like you.
I said yes without any hesitation.
That day,
I gave myself
to him.
I thought
even if we weren't rich,
at least I'd have a soulmate.
But who knew,
this person would suddenly disappear
from my world.
Disappear,
you know?
Vanished into thin air.
That morning,
we were still working
together in the hotel.
I went out to buy lunch at noon.
When I came back...
It's me, Yanfei.
Open the door. I don't have my key card.
I brought the food back for you.
What's wrong, young lady?
My boyfriend and I are preparing
for a dance drama here.
I guess he went out.
Could you please open the door for me?
A young man was staying in this room.
Tall and thin.
Yes, yes, yes.
You remember him, right?
Yes.
He checked out and left.
Checked out?
That's impossible.
We were still preparing here this morning.
Please open the door for me.
Let me go in and take a look.
Hello.
Can I borrow the phone?
Please page 987-03597 for me.
My last name is Shen.
Leave a message for me.
Tell me why.
Excuse me, can I borrow the phone again?
Please page 987-0357 again.
My last name is Shen.
Leave another message for me.
If you don't reply to me...
I won't be able to live on.
Li Xingchen, Yu Xiaotong
Song Yanfei, Wang Zhiyong (Wang Ruizi)
You Xi, Xie Tiantian
Special Appearance
(in order of strokes of Chinese surname)
Xiao Ze, Wang Hao
Feng Shu, Liu Yakun
Jiang Dahai, Liu Zheting (Liu Zheting)
Bai Sha, Li Xintong
Mu Liyan, Chen Yongxia
Weng Wei, Huang Fei (Huang Jingxin)
Gao Yuhai, Cao Haitao (Cao Jingshi)
Forensic Doctor, Cheng Gong
Li Xingchen's Classmate, Liu Haohan
Young Li Xingchen, Li Yuanche
Young Song Yanfei, Chen Nuoyan
Investor, Zha Minxin
Lead Singer, Xu Weina
Li Xingchen's Classmate, Gao Jingman
Xiao Ze's Mother, Zhao Yue'en
Xiao Ze's Relatives, Li Ming, Wang Zhilei
Hu Qin
Zhao Wenjuan, Li Ziying
Special Guest Female Classmate, Yue Yue
Yao Sha
Li Xingchen's Classmates,
Tang Tang, Dai Guoming
Woman, Sun Meili
Nanny, Wang Chunyang
Shareholders, Huang Xinyang, Wang Wentao
Gao Yuhai's Secretary, Du Du
Feng Shu's Secretary, Dai Dai
Drivers, Wang Yiguo, Liang
Old Man Walking Bird, Wang Jiasheng
Waiters, Liu Jiaqi, Dai Guoming
Aunties, Tu Manxia, Huang Xinyang
Middle-aged Man, Wang Xinda
Driver Zhao, Wei Hong
Qin Zhiqiang
Stagehand Zhang
Police Colleague
Mr. Xiong, Liu Junjie
Driver, Hu Huazheng
Scrap Yard Boss Zhang, Li Chenghu
Company Head, Bai Yongjun
Female Nurse, Bai Wanting
Guo Xinye
Spoken Word Contestants Nan Xi, Xu Ziyi
Man in Black Zhu Yiqi
Bai Xiaosi's Stand-in Zhao Peng
Li Xingchen's Stand-in Tang Li
Taxi Driver
Song Yucheng, Liang Zhengchao
Cashier Wu Tiantian
Yan Yongmei, Li Tianjun
Actor Hu Zexuan
Cleaner Liu
Extras Da Qing, Liu Haohan
Receptionist Xiaoyu Ren Jiefei
Crew
Chief Presenter Xu Yue
Co-Presenters Feng Fei, Guo Zhiyuan
Chief Distributor Hu Kaichen
Police Consultant / Original Story Fu Jun
Production Team
Chief Producers Sui Dalong, Gao Jingman
Producers Sui Sanlong, Li Xin
Executive Producers Peng Xia, Kang Hairu
Planner Zhao Feng
Production Manager Liu Zhilong
Welfare Manager Yin Zhongheng
Liu Xinyu
Set Operations
Key Grip Liu Yiqing
Yang Qunbao
Catering
Catering Manager Yin Xiumei
Vegetable Washer Hu Xiuxia
Li Zhiwei, Ma Yuan
Zheng Xiaorong
Zhang Meijuan
Liang Hui
Song Shuwei
Xiao Yucai, Liu Xin
Screenwriter Yue Shun
Script Supervisor
On-set Assistant Director Liu Haohan
Editing Team
DIT Jin Linxin
Production Designer Zhao Daqian
Co-Production Designer Gong Xueyuan
Assistant Art Director Wang Tianyi
Prop Art
Property Master Sun Donghua
On-set Prop Assistant Li Yao
Set Dressers Zhang Li, Zhang Qingzhong
Director of Photography Li Yixu
Camera A Operator He Yong
Camera A Assistant Li Xinghan
Camera B Operator Zhao Shidian
Camera B Assistant Cao Xing
Camera C Operator Ma Mingguo
Photographer
Camera Grips Guo Ruicai, Liu Shihao
Li Chen
Lighting Team
Gaffer Gao Yun
Te Rigun
Styling Team
Hair & Makeup Yuan Zihan, Wang Peng
On-set Wardrobe Supervisors
Zhang Lei, Yi Junli
Marketing & Distribution Team
Planning Director Yang Liuting
Graphic Design
Post-Production
Beijing Wenhui Qiming Culture
Communication Co., Ltd.
Post-Production Coordinator Zhang Xiaoman
Colorist Niu Xuerui
End Credits Jin Linxin
Re-recording Mixer Zhang Kai
Ambience Editor Zhang Xinyu
Sound Effects Editor Zhang Xiaoman
Visual Effects
VFX Supervisor Gao Dong
VFX Artist Jin Linxin
Shang Chenyao
Music Production
Hong Kong Musical Theatre, China
Music Director: Xiao Zhuang
Score Production: Xiao Zhuang, Wang Daifu
Music Coordinator: Jiang Zheng, Liu Zining
Cello: Zi Long
Score Mixing: Zhao Yi
Vocal Recording: Zheng Suyang
Recording Studio:
Beijing Landuo Recording Studio
"Brothers"
Vocals: Yue Shunming
Arrangement: Zhao Yi
Vocals: Zhang Keying
Lyrics: Yue Shunming
Composer: Xiao Zhuang
Producer
"Promise"
Composer: Xiao
Vocals: Ben Damiao
Lyrics: Xu Yue
Composer: Xu Yue
Vocals: Xu Yue
Arrangement: Wang Anyu
Lyrics: Fan Fan
Producer: Xu Yue
Lyrics: Bai Yuxiang
"Only You" (Russian)
Vocals: Liu Ruixun
Composer: Xiao
Arrangement: Zhao Yi
Publicity Department
of Shiyan Municipal Party Committee
Shiyan Public Security Bureau
Hubei Zhi Yuxuan
Agricultural Technology Co., Ltd.
Hubei Jiutouniao Catering Management
Shiyan Dongfeng Hometown
Historical Materials Exhibition Hall
Shiyan Xiaowujia Catering
Management Service Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Hengjiu Kanghua Real Estate
Co., Ltd. (Longcheng Fudi)
Zesheng Property Service Co., Ltd.
Sunshine Dance Art Training School,
Maojian District, Shiyan
Meiyijia Convenience Store, No. 88
Gongyuan Road, Zhangwan District, Shiyan
Co-production Companies
Sichuan Jiaodian Pictures Co., Ltd.
Sichuan Lengjing Chuangjie
Film and Television Culture Co., Ltd.
Shanxi Chengyi Film
and Television Media Co., Ltd.
Qinghe (Beijing) Culture Media Co., Ltd.